Guide to the Frank Espada photographs and papers, 1946-2010 and undated, bulk 1964-2000 RL.00367
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Frank Espada photographs and papers
1946-2010
1964-2000
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Espada, Frank, 1930-
Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University)
RL.00367
56.2 Linear Feet 76 boxes; 3 oversize folders approximately 14,500 items
Frank Espada was a political activist and documentary photographer of Puerto Rican extraction based in New York and California. His photographic archives comprise thousands of black-and-white photographs and negatives and related materials concerning Espada's lifelong work documenting the Puerto Rican diaspora, civil and economic rights movements, indigenous Chamorro communities in Micronesia, and HIV/AIDS outreach in San Francisco. The Puerto Rican Diaspora project also includes over 150 oral history recordings. The Civil Rights series documents voter registration and school desegregation rallies in New York City, 1964-1970, as well as housing and anti-poverty movements, primarily in California. Photographic subjects encompass Puerto Ricans, African Americans, and indigenous peoples, as well as whites and racially mixed people. The professional papers include files related to activism, research and writings, exhibits, teaching, and publicity. The earliest dated item is a 1946 essay by Espada, "What democracy means to me." Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by project series followed by other formats and papers: Chamorro Documentary Project; Civil Rights and Community Activism; HIV/AIDS Projects; Puerto Rican Diaspora; Other Work; Negatives; Papers; and Audiovisual Recordings.
Biographical Note
Frank Espada (1930-2014) was an American photojournalist, photographer, activist, educator, and community organizer. He was born December 21, 1930 in Utuado, Puerto Rico as Francisco Luis Espada Roig. His family emigrated to New York City in 1939. He attended City College of New York but cut his studies short to join the U.S. Air Force during the Korean War. Espada married his wife, Marilyn, in 1952; together they raised two boys and one girl - Jason, Lisa, and Martín. After the war, Espada attended The New York Institute of Photography in New York City, where his mentors were W. Eugene Smith and Dave Heath. To support his family, he worked as an electrical contractor for ten years.
Galvanized by social and economic inequities he witnessed in the late 1950s, Espada began working as a community organizer in New York City's most vulnerable and impoverished areas, and organized strikes against unfair rent increases, voter registration drives, sit-ins of welfare recipients and mothers, public school boycotts, and marches for civil and political rights. In 1979, he was awarded a grant from the National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) to document Puerto Rican communities in the U.S. as well as those who returned to Puerto Rico. From 1990 to 1992, he undertook the Chamorro Documentary Project, documenting indigenous peoples' lives in Micronesia.
In 1985, he and his family moved to San Francisco, where he continued his activism, chiefly related to housing rights, the eradication of poverty, and education reform; he also worked with Mid-City Coalition for HIV Prevention in San Francisco to document and improve AIDS outreach. He became a photography teacher for the University of California, Berkeley, Extension Program, and taught photography at the Academy of Art University and the San Francisco Art Institute. In 2006, he published The Puerto Rican Diaspora: Themes in the Survival of a People, and in 2008, received an honorary Doctor of Arts degree from Lehman College, Bronx, New York.
Frank Espada died in New York City, February 16, 2014, at the age of 83. His documentary photographs have been exhibited around the world at the Museum of Art in Chicago; Museo del Barrio, New York City; Honolulu Hale; the Museo de Arte in Ponce, Puerto Rico; and Duke University's Rubenstein Library, among others.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Original audiovisual media may need to be reformatted before use. Oral histories on cassettes have been digitized and are available upon request.
Please contact the Rubenstein Library before coming to use this collection.
Provenance
The Frank Espada photographs and papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase from 2010-2013.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
The photographs in this collection are all traditional process gelatin silver paper and some resin-coated prints; most were created by Espada within a year or two of image capture.
Negatives are chiefly 35 mm safety film strips and are closed to use for preservation reasons.
Collection Overview
Frank Espada's photographic archives comprise thousands of photographic prints, contact sheets, and negatives, as well as professional papers, spanning the length of Frank Espada's career as a photographer and community activist from the mid-1950s through 2010. The materials document the Puerto Rican diaspora; indigenous Chamorro communities in Micronesia, primarily in Guam, Tinian, and Saipan; drug abuse prevention programs and HIV/AIDS outreach in San Francisco; and civil rights, education, and anti-poverty and housing rights movements, primarily in New York City and San Francisco. Photographic subjects include Puerto Ricans, African Americans, and indigenous peoples, as well as whites and racially mixed people.
A large series of professional papers provides supporting documentation of his life and work as a photographer, activist, community organizer, and teacher. The earliest dated item, an essay Espada wrote in 1946, "What democracy means to me," is found in this series, which contains files on Espada's activism; research topics; photography and exhibits; a few videocassettes; syllabi and notes from his photography courses at U.C. Berkeley; awards and memorabilia; and publicity.
The largest body of materials, which numbers over 12,000 items and includes photographs as well as manuscripts and over 100 recorded oral interviews (digitized use copies available), derives from Espada's grant-funded work documenting Puerto Rican communities across the U.S. and in Puerto Rico, 1979-1981.
Another significant group of materials derives from Espada's activism on behalf of voter registration and school desegregation in New York City from 1962-1970, and later in California in support of anti-poverty, HIV/AIDS, drug abuse prevention and outreach, and housing rights.
Each of the photographic project series includes finished prints ranging in size from 8x10 to 24x30 inches; contact sheets and work prints; and negatives, which are housed in a separate series and are closed to use.
Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Related Materials
Related collection: Frank Espada photographs, 1968-2008, Archives Center, National Museum of American History, Washington, D.C.
African Americans -- Photographs; AIDS (Disease) -- Prevention; Chamorro (Micronesian people) -- Portraits; Civil rights movements -- United States -- 20th century -- Photographs; Documentary photography; Indigenous peoples -- Portraits; Photography of immigrants; Portrait photography; Puerto Ricans -- Portraits; Puerto Ricans -- United States -- Social conditions; Racially mixed people -- United States -- Pictorial works; Connecticut -- Photographs; Guam -- Photographs; Hawaii -- Photographs; Micronesia -- Photographs; New York (N.Y.) -- History -- 1951-; New York (N.Y.) -- Photographs; Pennsylvania -- Photographs; Puerto Rico -- Photographs; San Francisco (Calif.) -- Photographs; United States -- Emigration and immigration; United States -- Race relations -- History -- 20th century; Audiocassettes; Black-and-white photographs; Contact sheets; Gelatin silver prints; Negatives (photographs); Oral histories (document genre); Video recordings; Puerto Rican Diaspora Documentary Project; Espada, Frank, 1930-; Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University)
- Chamorro Documentary Project, 1989-1990; 2.5 Linear Feet 5 boxes Approximately 1572 items
  Scope and Contents
  In 1990, Frank Espada was asked by his friend and colleague from Chicago, Samuel Betances, to photograph the indigenous Chamorro people of Guam, Saipan, Titian and Rota in the Mariana Islands. Modeled after Espada's Puerto Rican Diaspora project, the aim of this project was to chronicle the Chamorro culture as well as the social challenges faced by this group, whose diaspora includes Hawaii and California. Some of the photographs in this series were taken at a Chamorro festival in California, but most were taken on Guam, the island with the largest concentration of Chamorro people. One series of about 290 work prints documents the funeral procession and expressions of protest after the suicide of former Guam governor Ricardo Bordallo in February 1990. Specific projects, programs, and protests are described in the photograph or folder titles. Most titles are retained from the originals.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Work or proof prints are typically sized 3 1/2 x 5 inches. Many work prints bear stamps on the back with the project title, theme, subjects, date, and original identification number.
  Specific locations, subjects and dates are reflected in print and folder titles, as originally assigned by the photographer. In some cases, multiple date markings on finished prints may reflect the date taken and date printed.
  - Finished Prints, 1990; 78 prints
    - Terry's Chamorro Food Counter, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0001)
      Image dimensions: 8 3/4 x 13 1/4 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Cantan Chamorritas: singing group, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0002)
      Image dimensions: 9 x 13 1/4 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Lunch break under the trees, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0003)
    - Boy on bicycle in front of church, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0004)
    - Above ground cemetery, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0005)
    - Cathedral with statue in front, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0006)
    - Naputi family sitting on bench, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0007)
    - Nun and children (all children of ROTA), Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0008)
    - Children at desks, pretty girl leaning on desk, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0009)
    - Loling with her class at Guam U, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0010)
    - High school students in Guam (on steps), 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0011)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/4 x 8 3/4 inches; sheet dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Senior citizens playing bridge, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0012)
      Image dimensions: 8 7/8 x 13 1/4 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Young woman with cap, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0013)
    - Politician with Panama hat and alligator shirt, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0014)
    - High school girls' group sitting on floor, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0015)
      Image dimensions: 8 7/8 x 13 1/4; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Poster girl (Stephanie), Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0016)
    - National Guard leader with sword, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0017)
    - Sweetheart couple sitting with feet in river, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0018)
    - Young boy with soda can, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0019)
    - Pretty little girl with bangs, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0020)
    - Four teenagers on couch outside house, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0021)
    - Tour guide, Saipan, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0022)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/4 x 9 inches; sheet dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Wood carver with bandana, Saipan, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0023)
    - Young people performing native dance, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0024)
    - Gay leader, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0025)
    - Man with flower shirt (son of dispossessed family, land taken by US Air Force), Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0026)
      Image dimensions: 9 1/8 x 13 1/4 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Mr. Naputi (fisherman), Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0027)
    - Young man with gold chain and amulet, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0028)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/4 x 9 1/8 inches; sheet dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Two boys in friendly embrace, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0029)
    - Man with aviator glasses, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0030)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/4 x 8 7/8 inches; sheet dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Young woman with class ring, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0031)
    - Classroom in ROTA, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0032)
    - Man with mustache and hand on face, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0033)
    - Young man with "DLN" and heart-shaped tattoo on arm, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0034)
    - Young woman with striped shirt playing ukulele, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0035)
    - Beautiful children of various backgrounds in story-telling class, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0036)
    - Very old lady with big glasses (senior citizens' club), Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0037)
    - Beautiful child with puppy, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0038)
    - Brother and his sister - she has a Barbie necklace, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0039)
    - Girl receiving Loling's gold necklace as present - total surprise!, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0040)
    - Woman with big glasses and hand to chin, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0041)
    - Young man with crew cut, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0042)
    - Young kid sitting on stoop, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0043)
    - Young girl with hand on head, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0044)
    - Inside Chamorro grocery store, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0045)
    - Little kid looking at big hogs in pen, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0046)
    - Young woman in refuge house - cross earrings, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0047)
    - "I Love Justice" - on way to Bordallo funeral march, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0048)
    - "I Love Justice" - on way to Bordallo funeral march, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0049)
    - Young man with flag in Bordallo funeral march, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0050)
    - Young man with flag in Bordallo funeral march, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0051)
    - Farmer with cigarette - holding leaves, Guam, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL.00367-P-0052)
    - Doctor examining patient at clinic, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0053)
    - Woman in wheelchair, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0054)
    - Good-looking kid with Aloha shirt, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0055)
    - Japan Town, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0056)
    - Japan Town, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0057)
    - Old man with big glasses, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0058)
    - Man with raised hand at political meeting, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0059)
    - Woman with five children at Bordallo funeral, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0060)
    - Little girl with ponytail, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0061)
    - Little girl standing at beach, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0062)
    - Little boy with sandals sitting on steps, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0063)
    - Future Guam representative (man), Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0064)
    - Man with glasses and Zapata mustache, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0065)
    - Mother cuddling her daughter (old lady in background), Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0066)
    - Girl leaning on concrete fence, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0067)
    - Woman sitting in park with indigenous totems, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0068)
      Image dimensions: 9 1/4 x 13 1/4 inches; sheet dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Two young girl friends - with earrings, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0069)
    - Building Japan Town, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0070)
    - Tailor cutting material, Saipan, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0071)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/4 x 9 1/4 inches; sheet dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Loling and students in her classroom, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0072)
    - Four doctors standing in front of clinic (educated in US and returned to Guam), Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0073)
    - Man in front of sign: "Guam's quest for commonwealth," Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0074)
    - Man in front of sign: "Guam's quest for commonwealth," Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0075)
    - Young girl with striped blouse - loving look and bright smile, Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0076)
    - Old lady laughing - covering her mouth (Senior Center), Guam, 1990 (Box 2, Image RL.00367-P-0077)
    - Saipan: Woodworker, 1990 (Box 54, Image RL.00367-P-0078)
      Image dimensions: 12 1/4 x 18 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
  - Contact Sheets and Work Prints, 1989-1990; 1494 items
    Subseries contains contact sheets created from negative strips, and selected images in the form of small work prints from which Espada then selected images for larger finished prints. Some contact sheets are missing; these are noted whenever possible. Folder titles are taken from the originals.
    - Chamorro Festival
      - Vallejo, California, contact sheets 1-10, 1989; 10 items (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Micronesia
      - Contact sheets 1-50, missing 29-32, 1990; 46 items (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Contact sheets 51-99, missing 90-96, 1990; 42 items (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Contact sheets 100-144, 1990; 45 items (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Contact sheets 145-192, missing 153,157,167,186-188, 1990; 42 items (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Work prints: Micronesia, 1990; 164 items (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Work prints: Micronesia, 1990; 165 items (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: Micronesia, 1990; 171 items (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Work prints: Micronesia, 1990; 155 items (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: At a friend's house, 1990; 20 items (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Work prints: Documentation of funeral of Ricardo Bordallo, former governor of Guam (folder 1 of 8), 1990 February 10; 40 items (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Documentation of funeral of Ricardo Bordallo, former governor of Guam (folder 2 of 8), 1990 February 10; 40 items (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Documentation of funeral of Ricardo Bordallo, former governor of Guam (folder 3 of 8), 1990 February 10; 40 items (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Documentation of funeral of Ricardo Bordallo, former governor of Guam (folder 4 of 8), 1990 February 10; 40 items (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Documentation of funeral of Ricardo Bordallo, former governor of Guam (folder 5 of 8), 1990 February 10; 40 items (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Documentation of funeral of Ricardo Bordallo, former governor of Guam (folder 6 of 8), 1990 February 10; 40 items (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Documentation of funeral of Ricardo Bordallo, former governor of Guam (folder 7 of 8), 1990 February 10; 40 items (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Documentation of funeral of Ricardo Bordallo, former governor of Guam (folder 8 of 8), 1990 February 10; 12 items (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Work prints: Japanese town - Agaña, circa 1990; 22 items (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Work prints: Japanese baseball players - training in Guam (folder 1 of 2), circa 1990; 40 items (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Work prints: Japanese baseball players - training in Guam (folder 2 of 2), circa 1990; 21 items (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Work prints: Loling's family at Geri's (folder 1 of 2), circa 1990; 40 items (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Work prints: Loling's family at Geri's (folder 2 of 2), circa 1990; 26 items (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Work prints: Loling's class, circa 1990; 40 items (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Work prints: Miscellaneous, circa 1990; 40 items (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: Miscellaneous, circa 1990; 28 items (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Work prints: Saipan party, circa 1990; 40 items (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Work prints: Saipan party, circa 1990; 29 items (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Work prints: Senior citizens program, circa 1990; 16 items (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Civil Rights and Community Activism, 1960s-1997; 3.5 Linear Feet 6.5 boxes Approximately 724 items
  Images document Espada's long and passionate involvement in early civil rights movements pursuing equal rights in voting, education, access to food, medical facilities, housing, and neighborhood development. He began by photographing voter registration drives in the early 1960s, desegregation protests and rallies, political campaigns by progressive candidates, and blighted, impoverished neighborhoods. Later, he also documented anti-poverty and housing rights actions in California, especially in San Francisco. Specific projects, programs, and protests are described in the photograph or folder titles. Materials are arranged roughly in order by decade. Most titles are retained from the originals.
  - Finished Prints, 1963-1964, 1974; 51 prints
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0079)
      Related Materials
      Image dimensions: 7 3/8 x 9 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 8 1/8 x 10 1/8 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0080)
      Image dimensions: 6 7/8 x 5 7/8 inches; mount dimensions: 10 x 8 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0081)
      Image dimensions: 8 x 5 1/4 inches; mount dimensions: 10 x 8 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0082)
      Image dimensions: 6 x 8 5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 7 7/8 x 10 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0083)
      Image dimensions: 5 x 8 1/8 inches; mount dimensions: 8 x 10 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0084)
      Image dimensions: 5 3/8 x 8 7/8 inches; mount dimensions 8 x 10 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0085)
      Image dimensions: 5 3/4 x 8 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 8 x 10 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0086)
      Image dimensions: 8 x 5 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 8 x 10 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0087)
      Image dimensions: 8 1/8 x 5 inches; mount dimensions: 8 x 10 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0088)
      Image dimensions: 7 7/8 x 5 1/8 inches; mount dimensions: 8 x 10 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0089)
      Image dimensions: 6 x 8 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 8 x 10 inches
    - Mr. Jackson, Brooklyn, 1963 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0090)
      Image dimensions: 9 5/8 x 5 7/8 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - Long Island City, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0091)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/2 x 10 1/2 inches; sheet dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - School boycott, Brooklyn, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0092)
      Image dimensions: 10 7/8 x 7 7/8 inches; sheet dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
    - Voter registration, Brownsville, Brooklyn, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0093)
      Image dimensions: 13 1/2 x 9 inches; mount dimensions: 13 1/2 x 9 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0094)
      Image dimensions: 6 x 9 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0095)
      Image dimensions: 5 3/4 x 8 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches
    - No known title, 1964 (Box 7, Image RL.00367-P-0096)
      Image dimensions: 6 1/2 x 9 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 14 inches